[
    {
        "numb": 1,
        "question": "What is the first step in the software development lifecycle?",
        "answer": "Preliminary Investigation and Analysis",
        "options": [
            "System Design",
            "Coding",
            "System Testing",
            "Preliminary Investigation and Analysis"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 2,
        "question": "What does the study of an existing system refer to?",
        "answer": "System Analysis",
        "options": [
            "Details of DFD",
            "Feasibility Study",
            "System Analysis",
            "System Planning"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 3,
        "question": "Which of the following is involved in the system planning and designing phase of the Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "options": [
            "Sizing",
            "Parallel run",
            "Specification freeze",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 4,
        "question": "What does RAD stand for?",
        "answer": "Rapid Application Development",
        "options": [
            "Rapid Application Development",
            "Rapid Application Document",
            "Relative Application Development",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 5,
        "question": "Which of the following prototypes does not associated with Prototyping Model?",
        "answer": "Diagonal Prototype",
        "options": [
            "Domain Diagram",
            "Diagonal Prototype",
            "Horizontal Prototype",
            "Sequence Diagram"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 6,
        "question": "Interaction Diagram is a combined term for",
        "answer": "Sequence Diagram + Collaboration Diagram",
        "options": [
            "Activity Diagram + State Chart Diagram",
            "Sequence Diagram + Collaboration Diagram",
            "Deployment Diagram + Collaboration Diagram",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 7,
        "question": "The major drawback of RAD model is __",
        "answer": "Both (a) & (c)",
        "options": [
            "It requires highly skilled developers/designers.",
            "It necessitates customer feedbacks.",
            "It increases the component reusability.",
            "Both (a) & (c)"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 8,
        "question": "Which of the following diagram is time oriented?",
        "answer": "Sequence",
        "options": [
            "Collaboration",
            "Activity",
			"Sequence",
			"None of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 9,
        "question": "As the instructions can deal with variable size operands we use ____________ to resolve this.",
        "answer": "Size indicator mnemonic",
        "options": [
            "None of the mentioned",
            "Size indicator mnemonic",
            "Special assemblers",
            "Delimiter"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 10,
        "question": "How many diagrams are here in Unified Modelling Language?",
        "answer": "nine",
        "options": [
            "eight",
            "nine",
            "seven",
            "six"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 11,
        "question": "Which of the following does not relate to Evolutionary Process Model?",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "options": [
            "Incremental Model",
            "Concurrent Development Model",
            "WINWIN Spiral Model",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 12,
        "question": "who consider diagrams as a type of Class diagram, component diagram, object diagram, and deployment diagram?",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "options": [
            "structural",
            "behavioral",
            "non-behavioral",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 13,
        "question": "What is the major drawback of the Spiral Model?",
        "answer": "Doesn't work well for smaller projects",
        "options": [
            "Higher amount of risk analysis",
            "Strong approval and documentation control",
            "Additional functionalities are added later on",
            "Doesn't work well for smaller projects"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 14,
        "question": ".__________ represented by In UML diagrams, relationship between component parts and object.",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "options": [
            "Requirements",
            "Development team & users",
            "Project type & associated risk",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 15,
        "question": "Model selection is based on _",
        "answer": "The address for the next instruction",
        "options": [
            "The accumulated memory location",
            "The instruction for the next instruction",
            "The data for the next instruction",
            "The address for the next instruction"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 16,
        "question": "which type they considered Activity diagram, use case diagram, collaboration diagram, and sequence diagram?",
        "answer": "behavioral",
        "options": [
            "structural",
            "non-structural",
            "non-behavioral",
            "behavioral"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 17,
        "question": "Which of the following models doesn't necessitate defining requirements at the earliest in the lifecycle?",
        "answer": "Spiral & Prototyping",
        "options": [
            "Compression",
            "Prototyping & Waterfall",
            "Spiral & RAD",
            "Spiral & Prototyping"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 18,
        "question": "simple name in UML Class and objects consist of __________.",
        "answer": "All of the mentioned",
        "options": [
            "Letters",
			"Digits",
			"Punctuation Characters",
            "All of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 19,
        "question": "which of these abstractions class consist?",
        "answer": "All of the mentioned",
        "options": [
            "Attributes",
            "Operations",
            "Set of the objects",
            "All of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 20,
        "question": "which of the following attribute is a data item held by?",
        "answer": "All of the mentioned",
        "options": [
            "Class",
            "Object",
            "All of the mentioned",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    }
]